

SHREYA KUMRAWAT

SME - Web Designer

8962129334

shreya_kumrawat@yahoo.com



Mumbai

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Application ICS (Vikram Universitr) Ujjain M.P. 2014

Bachelor of Computer Application BIPS M.P. (MCU Bhopal) 2011

Higher Secondary (10+2) Lokmanya Tilak School Ujjain M.P Board Bhopal 2008

High School Lokmanya Tilak School Ujjain M.P. Board Bhopal 2006

SKILLS

- Team Management
- HTML
- CSS, BEM
- WordPress
- Angular 6
- Illustrator
- Photoshop
- Bootstrap
- Adobe XD
- **JQuery**
- JavaScript

ABOUT ME

With 8 years of total experience, I have a good understanding of design creation, Angular 6, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, media queries, JQuery, and Visual Studio code editor. Capacity to identify and handle challenging difficulties is seen as a sign of a good troubleshooter. exposure to all Waterfall Methodologies and SDLC phases.

As a SME, it is my responsibility to ensure that the information is accurate so that the project or program's deliverables meet stakeholder needs, legal requirements, industry best practices, and standards.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SME Web Designer

May 2024 - Current

Datamatics Business Solutions

- Based on the needs of the customer, a standardization code for the landing page
- Ensure that everyone in the team adheres to the same standardization code.
- Establishing a Weekly Changes Update Portal to fulfill the unique needs of the Stakeholders, enabling us to maintain the tracking of client updates

Officer Web Designer

May 2021 - May 2024

Datamatics Business Solutions

- Creating an Email Template HTML and Landing page for relevant primary clients like Intensify, Thomson Reuters, PROS, Interlink, Veeam, AWS, IBM, Spiceworks, and Microsoft.
- Allocating tasks to the agents and Quality check for the final outcome.
- HTML and Landing page testing.
- Working closely with marketing team for the performance of the creative.

Web Developer

Feb 2019 - Feb 2021

Tekskills India Pvt Ltd.

- BITS The system is used for the helpdesk where employees call the request for their System issues, Network requirements, Internet issues etc.
- BITA + UI Revamps IT asset management in BITA+ application and provide an overview for the online application to streamline many activities about procurement, distribution, commissioning, maintenance, buyback, and disposal of IT.
- BPCL Modify the existing template of BPCL.
- Creating web pages using Asp.Net MVC, Angular6, Bootstrap, CSS, Design, GIF images, and icons, Visual Studio 2017 Community.

REFERENCE

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shreya-kumrawat-8440a816a/

Portfolio

https://myblog-v.web.app/

Github

https://aithub.com/anshulkumrawat?tab=repositories

YouTube Channel

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC0t7RK5ldMtwBShWipAEABg

Behance

https://www.behance.net/shreyakumrawat

Junior Web Developer

Oct 2017 - Oct 2018

Veniteck Solutions

- Building social media creative post and design layout logos, Certificate, PSD Layouts several clients such as Cowan-Air, Door, Tools & Gear, Symphony Events, Fabbuyz, Veniteck Solutions, PHKA, IReady Today
- Development and design on JQuery, Angular6, HTML, and CSS.
- Involved inwriting application-level code to interact with APIs, Web Services using AJAX\JSON, and Angular6. Managing and implementing all code changes with Bitbucket.
- Design and developement on JavaScript, JSON Photoshop, HTML, Bootstrap, Angular6, Node.js, Firebase Console, and Photoshop. Various multiple styles with colors, fonts, and backgounds in CSS.
- Extensively involved design discussion with the client.

Web Designer

Jan 2016 - Nov 2016

Obabuji.com

- Designed the Front-End applications, User Interactive (UI) web pages Worked extensively with the Image Libraries.
- Developed UI using JavaScript, HTML / HTML5, DOM, CSS, JQuery.
- Used web technologies like HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and Photoshop.

.Net Developer

Jun 2015 - Dec 2015

Mahakal Web Technologies

- Hotel Paradise Ujjain This website is developed for online Room Booking for Visitors.
- Worked on the frontend JavaScript, HTML / HTML5, DOM, AJAX, CSS, and JQuery

Web Developer

Aug 2014 - Jun 2015

Brilliance Pvt. Ltd

- GDC College Ujjain This website is developed for online admission only for girls.
- Developed non-functional HTML, and CSS pages from the mockups.